Guide to the Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1973-2015; Series I; 23.25; 25 boxes
  - Alphabetical correspondence
    - Roth, Cindy, 1989-1990, undated (Box 16)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome, 1995 July 25 (Box 16)
    - Rothschild, Doug, 1991 (Box 16)
    - Roundy, Richard, 1995 (Box 16)
    - Roy, Camille, 1984-1995, undated; 2 (Box 16)
    - Royet-Joumoud, Claude, 1996-1997, undated (Box 16)
    - Russell, Arthur, 1977-2006, undated (Box 16)
    - Russell, Christopher, 2004, undated; 2 (Box 16)
    - Russell, John, undated (Box 16)
    - Ryan, Tracy, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Sabino, Osvaldo, 1998 September 21 (Box 16)
    - Saidenberg, Jocelyn, 1996, undated (Box 16)
    - Sakkis, John, undated (Box 16)
    - Salerno, Mark, 1995-1996, undated (Box 16)
    - SF Camerawork, 1989, undated (Box 16)
    - Sand, Kaia, 2004, undated (Box 16)
    - Santiago, Sergio, 1989-1993, undated (Box 16)
    - Saren, Dru, 1995 July 05 (Box 16)
    - Scalapino, Leslie, 1987-2006, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Schluter, Kit, 2003 February 14 (Box 17)
    - Schaefer, Standard, undated (Box 17)
    - Schaffner, Igrid, 2007 (Box 17)
    - Schelling, Andrew, 2003-2006, undated (Box 17)
    - Schimel, Lawrence, 1995-1998, undated (Box 17)
    - Schlagel, Anthony, 1992, undated (Box 17)
    - Schlesinger, 2008, undated (Box 17)
    - Scholder, Amy, 1989-1993, undated (Box 17)
    - Schulman, Sarah, 1989-2005, undated (Box 17)
    - Schultz, Charles M., 1997 June 27 (Box 17)
    - Schultz, Fritz, 1989-1996, undated (Box 17)
    - Schultz, Kathy Lou, 1993-1996, undated (Box 17)
    - Schultz, Susan, 1996, undated (Box 17)
    - Schuyler, James, 1987, undated (Box 17)
    - Schwartz, Jay, 1995, undated (Box 17)
    - Schwartz, Leonard, 1992 January 21 (Box 17)
    - Schwemer, Armand, 1991 March 22 (Box 17)
    - Scobel, Jenny, 1994 December 05 (Box 17)
    - Scott, Gail, 1993-2001, undated (Box 17)
    - Scott, Ramsey, 2008, undated (Box 17)
    - Scott, Travers, 1995-2003, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Seaton, Peter, 1996, undated (Box 17)
    - Secor, Kyle, 1988, undated (Box 17)
    - Sedaris, David, 1990, undated (Box 17)
    - Seifer, Jon, 1987, undated (Box 17)
    - Selby, Spencer, 1991-1992, undated (Box 17)
    - Selerie, Gavin, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Selwyn, Herb, 2004, undated (Box 17)
    - Servin, Jacques, undated (Box 17)
    - Shalom, Todd, undated (Box 17)
    - Shapazian, Robert, 1989, undated (Box 17)
    - Shaviro, Steve, 1981-1995, undated (Box 17)
    - Shaw, Francie, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Shaw, Jim, 1994 August 11 (Box 17)
    - Shaw, Lytle, 1998, undated (Box 17)
    - Shaw, Nancy, 1993 February 18 (Box 17)
    - Sheehan, David, 1982–1983 (Box 17)
    - Sheppard, Robert, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Sher, Gail, 1985-1987, undated (Box 17)
    - Sherburne, Philip, 1996 November 20 (Box 17)
    - Shimasaki, Paul, 1982-1989, undated (Box 17)
    - Shurin, Aaron, 1984-1997, undated (Box 17)
    - Sigo, Cedar, 1997-2004, undated (Box 17)
    - Sikelianos, Eleni, 1993-1997, undated (Box 17)
    - Silberman, Steve, 1985, undated (Box 17)
    - Silliman, Ron, 1995, undated (Box 17)
    - Silverberg, Ira, 1991–1993 (Box 17)
    - Simmons, Steve, 1993, undated (Box 17)
    - Simpson, Megan, 1989-1992, undated (Box 17)
    - Singer, Leslie, 1992-1994, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Singleton, Giovanni, undated (Box 17)
    - Skelley, Jack, undated (Box 17)
    - Slattery-Hunt, Liam, 1984, undated; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Slettery-Hunt, Liam, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Slosek, Michael, 2006, undated (Box 17)
    - Smithtown Sizzler, 1974-1980, undated (Box 17)
    - Skinner, Jimmy, 1988–1989 (Box 17)
    - Skinker, Will, 2007 January (Box 17)
    - Sloan, Margy, 1987, undated (Box 17)
    - Smith, Charles, 1995 September 13 (Box 17)
    - Smith, Colin, 1991-1992, undated (Box 17)
    - Smith, Dale, 1995-1997, undated (Box 17)
    - Smith, Ed, 1985–1987 (Box 17)
    - Smith, Gail, 1980 (Box 17)
    - Smith, Gail / John Mascaro, 1985-1986, undated (Box 17)
    - Smith, Logan Ryan, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Smith, Rod, 1992-1994, undated (Box 17)
    - Smith, Wayne, undated (Box 17)
    - Smith Nash, Susan, undated (Box 17)
    - Smithson, Gary, undated (Box 17)
    - Smock, Ann, 1987-1992, undated; 2 (Box 17)
    - Smoler, Michael, 2004, undated (Box 17)
    - Smukler, Linda, undated (Box 17)
    - Snell, Roger, 1998 May 08 (Box 17)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1993 April 17 (Box 17)
    - Soltesz, Natty, 2011, undated (Box 17)
    - Sonbert, Warren, undated (Box 17)
    - Southern Exposure Gallery, 1991 June 05 (Box 18)
    - Spahr, Juliana, 1992-1995, undated; 2 (Box 18)
    - Sparks, Amy, 1992-1993, undated (Box 18)
    - Spring, Justin, 2003 (Box 18)
    - Stadler, Matthew, 1990-2006, undated (Box 18)
    - Stambolian, George, 1985-1991, undated (Box 18)
    - Stanley, George, 1984-1995, undated (Box 18)
    - Stark, Frances, undated (Box 18)
    - Stavrides, Marie K., 1974–1988 (Box 18)
    - Stecopoulos, Eleni, undated (Box 18)
    - Stein, Suzanne, 2000-2004, undated (Box 18)
    - Steinbrecher, Matthew, 2014 January 06 (Box 18)
    - Steiner, Susan, 1985 September 10 (Box 18)
    - Stephenson, Ann, 2006-2007, undated (Box 18)
    - Stewart, Seth, 1997–2014 (Box 18)
    - Strang, Brian, 1996-1997, undated (Box 18)
    - Strang, Catriona, 1992-1993, undated (Box 18)
    - Strieber, Whitley, 1988 (Box 18)
    - Stoffolino, Chris, 1990-1993, undated (Box 18)
    - Stuart, Gaby, 1993 (Box 18)
    - Suits, Arthur, 1999 October 03 (Box 18)
    - Sullivan, Gary, 1991-1993, undated; 2 (Box 18)
    - Sumell, Matt, undated (Box 18)
    - Summers, Claude, 1994, undated (Box 18)
    - Sunny and Honey, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Susann, Jacqueline, undated (Box 18)
    - Sussman, Elizabeth, 1992 April 01 (Box 18)
    - Sweeney, Chad, undated (Box 18)
    - Swenson, Cole, 1988-1994, undated (Box 18)
    - Sycamore, Matt Bernstein, undated (Box 18)
    - Szymanski, Zak, undated (Box 18)
    - Taggert, John, 1991 January 05 (Box 18)
    - Tagett, Richard, 2006–2008 (Box 18)
    - Tang, Sikay, undated (Box 18)
    - Tangredi, Frank, 1982–1983 (Box 18)
    - Tam, Nathaniel, 1995, undated (Box 18)
    - Tarver, John, 1996, undated (Box 18)
    - Taylor, Brigham, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Taylor, Elizabeth, undated (Box 18)
    - Taylor, James, 1998, undated (Box 18)
    - Taylor, Steven, 2003 July 13 (Box 18)
    - Tea, Michelle, 2005 November (Box 18)
    - Tejada, Roberto, 2003 December 08 (Box 18)
    - Templeton, Fiona, 1992-1997, undated (Box 18)
    - Terrell, Matthew, undated (Box 18)
    - Thibodeaux, Sunnylyn, 2008, undated (Box 18)
    - Thomas, Lorenzo, undated (Box 18)
    - Thompson, Catherine Mary ("Kate"), 1981 May 06 (Box 18)
    - Thompson, Thomas, 1994, undated (Box 18)
    - Tierney, Karl, undated (Box 18)
    - Tillman, Lynne, 1987-1998, undated (Box 18)
    - Tills, Stephen, 1995, undated (Box 18)
    - Timmons, Susie, 1987, undated (Box 18)
    - Tinnin, Celia, 1990, undated (Box 18)
    - Tipping, Richard, 1994, undated (Box 18)
    - Tomkiw, Lydia, 1989 April 29 (Box 18)
    - Torra, Joseph, 1992-1996, undated (Box 18)
    - Torregian, Sotere, 2005 August 20 (Box 18)
    - Toscano, Rodrigo, 1995, undated (Box 18)
    - Townsend, Jamie, undated (Box 18)
    - Toxell, Jane, 1990, undated (Box 18)
    - Trachtenberg, Amy, undated (Box 18)
    - Trachtenberg, Paul, 1986 (Box 18)
    - Treleaven, Scott, 2009 November (Box 18)
    - Tremblay McGaw, Robin, 1996, undated (Box 18)
    - Trinidad, David, 1985-1993, undated; 2 (Box 18)
    - Tu, Hung Q., 1995-1996, undated (Box 18)
    - Tupitsyn, Masha, 2007 August 09 (Box 18)
    - Turner, Michael, undated (Box 18)
    - Tushinski, Jim, 1997 April (Box 18)
    - Twersky, Lori, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Tyrkus, Michael, 1996 January 06 (Box 18)
    - Tysh, Chris, 1987, undated (Box 18)
    - Tyson, Nicola, 1994, undated (Box 18)
    - Underwood, Jane, 1987, undated (Box 18)
    - Vacin, Eric, undated (Box 18)
    - van Buskirk, Jim, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Valente, Peter, 1994-1998, undated (Box 18)
    - Vena-Mondt, Carol, 1990-1991, undated (Box 19)
    - Veronese, David, 1991-1997, undated; 2 (Box 19)
    - Viegener, Matias, 1988-1991, undated (Box 19)
    - Vincent, John Emil, undated (Box 19)
    - Vining, Donald, undated (Box 19)
    - Virga, Vincent, 1983-1989, undated (Box 19)
    - Vogel, Traci, 2005, undated (Box 19)
    - Vose, Julia, 1987 July 07 (Box 19)
    - Wade, Valerie, 2008 July 21 (Box 19)
    - Wagner, James, 2001–2002 (Box 19)
    - Wagstaff, Christopher, 1994-2010, undated (Box 19)
    - Waldman, Anne, 1998-2008, undated (Box 19)
    - Waldrop, Keith, 2000, undated (Box 19)
    - Waldrop, Rosmarie, 1987-1996, undated (Box 19)
    - Wall, Tom, 1995, undated (Box 19)
    - Wallace, Jan, undated (Box 19)
    - Wallace, Mark, 1992-1994, undated (Box 19)
    - Wallin, Michael, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Walters, Minette, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Ward, Dana, undated (Box 19)
    - Ward, Diane, undated (Box 19)
    - Warland, Betsy, 1985, undated (Box 19)
    - Warren, Alli, 2005 November 13 (Box 19)
    - Waters, John, 1985-2004, undated (Box 19)
    - Watsky, Paul, undated (Box 19)
    - Watson, Scott, 1996-2004, undated (Box 19)
    - Watson, Steven, 2004 December 28 (Box 19)
    - Watten, Barrett, 1987-1994, undated; 2 (Box 19)
    - Watts, Charles, 1994-1996, undated (Box 19)
    - Weber, Lenora Mattingly, undated (Box 19)
    - Weeks, Laurie, 1992-1998, undated (Box 19)
    - Weiner, Hannah, 1989-1990, undated (Box 19)
    - Weiser, Karen, 2014 (Box 19)
    - Weiss, Jono, 1992-1993, undated (Box 19)
    - Weiss, Ruth, 2008 September 28 (Box 19)
    - Weissman, Benjamin, 1985-1987, undated (Box 19)
    - Welish, Marjorie, undated (Box 19)
    - Welt, Bernard, 1987-2000, undated (Box 19)
    - Weltner, Peter, 1993-1996, undated (Box 19)
    - West, Donna, 1994 December 19 (Box 19)
    - Westmoreland, Joe, 1993-1995, undated (Box 19)
    - Whalen, Philip, undated (Box 19)
    - Wheeler, Liz, 1983-1990, undated (Box 19)
    - Wheeler, Susan, 1991, undated (Box 19)
    - White Columns Exhibition 2006, 2006, undated (Box 19)
    - White, Edmund, 1990-1997, undated (Box 19)
    - White, Judy, 1981 March 08 (Box 19)
    - Whitmore, George, 1988, undated (Box 19)
    - Whitney, David, 1988-2005, undated (Box 19)
    - Wieners, John, 1989-2007, undated (Box 19)
    - Wildanger, Geoffrey, 2014 March (Box 19)
    - Wilde, Meta D., 1988–1989 (Box 19)
    - Wilkinson, John, 1985, undated (Box 19)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1991 (Box 19)
    - Williams, Michael, undated (Box 19)
    - Williams, Ron, 1983 June 28 (Box 19)
    - Williams, Tyrone, 2002, undated (Box 19)
    - Willis, Danielle, undated (Box 19)
    - Willis, Elizabeth, 1994-1999, undated (Box 19)
    - Willkie, Philip, 1984-1990, undated; 2 (Box 19)
    - Wills, Garry, 1998 February 18 (Box 19)
    - Wilson, Grant, 1993 Ocotober 07 (Box 19)
    - Windham, Donald, 1988, undated (Box 19)
    - Windham, Donald and Sandy Campbell, undated (Box 19)
    - Wing, Alicia, 1995-1999, undated (Box 19)
    - Witchey, Alan, undated (Box 19)
    - Wolf, Christa, 1993 (Box 19)
    - Wolf, Manfred, 1994-2001, undated (Box 19)
    - Wolsak, Melissa, undated (Box 19)
    - Wong, Erwin, 1982-1990, undated; 2 (Box 19)
    - Wright, Jay, 2003, undated (Box 19)
    - Yackulic, Will, undated (Box 19)
    - Yap, Christine Wong, undated (Box 19)
    - Yap, Timothy, 1997 (Box 19)
    - Yau, John, 1994–1996 (Box 19)
    - Young, Elizabeth, 1993 May 12 (Box 19)
    - Young, Geoff, 1989–1993 (Box 20)
    - Yuhas, Daniel, 1998, undated (Box 20)
    - Zapruder, Matthew, 2009 May 27 (Box 20)
    - Zawacki, Andrew, 2010 June 28 (Box 20)
    - Zorker, Jordon, 1993 March 11 (Box 20)
    - Zorn, John, undated (Box 20)
    - Zukowski, Peter, 1995 August 29 (Box 20)
    - Zurawski, Magdalena, 1991-1994, undated (Box 20)
    - Unidentified, 1983-1999, undated; 12 (Box 20)
  - Additional correspondence
    - A-L, 1978-2015, undated; 154 folders (Box 21)
    - M-Y, 1983-2015, undated; 116 folders (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995-2014, undated; 8 folders (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-2014, undated; 6 folders (Box 24)
    - A-W, 1977-2015, undated; 104 folders (Box 25)
- Writings, 1952-2014; Series II; 3.21; 4 boxes
  - Published works
    - Kevin Killian, Arctic Summer (Masquerade Books, 1997), 1952-1996, undated; 4 (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian, Argento Series (Krupskaya, 2001), 2000, undated; 2 (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian, Bedrooms Have Windows (Amethyst Press, 1990), 1989-1998, undated; 5 (Box 26)
    - Dody Bellamy, Broken English (Meow, 1996), undated (Box 26)
    - Dody Bellamy, Cunt-Ups (Tender Buttons, 2002), undated (Box 26)
    - Dody Bellamy, "The Debbies I Have Known" (Feminist Studies, Vol. ro, no. 2, Summer 1984), 1984-1991, undated; 2 (Box 26)
    - Dody Bellamy, Feminine Hijinx (Hanuman, 1991), 1990, undated; 3 (Box 26)
    - Dody Bellamy, Hallucinations (Meow, 1997), undated; 2 (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian, I Cry Like A Baby (Painted Leaf Press, 2001), 2000, undated; 2 (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian, Impossible Princess (City Lights, 2009), 2008, undated (Box 26)
    - Dody Bellamy, The Letters of Mina Harker (University of Wisconsin Press, 2004) (Box 26)
      - 4 July 79, undated (Box 26)
      - Bruce, undated (Box 26)
      - Days Without Someone, 1988-1989, undated (Box 26)
      - Dear Bill, 1989-1990, undated (Box 26)
      - Dear Cassandra, 1992, undated (Box 26)
      - Dear David, 1992; 2 (Box 26)
      - Dear Gail, 1992, undated; 3 (Box 26)
      - Dear Laurie, 1993 (Box 26)
      - Dear Leslie, 1991 (Box 26)
      - Dear Lynne, 1991 June 09 (Box 26)
      - Dear Patrick, 1991 (Box 26)
      - Dear Raymond, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Dear Sam, 1993 January 28 (Box 26)
      - December 2 1985, 1985 December 02 (Box 26)
      - July 13, 1985 (Kevin), 1985 July 13 (Box 26)
      - June 7, 1986 (To: Dr van Helsing), 1986, undated (Box 26)
      - Kevin, 1985, undated (Box 26)
      - Kevin/ Van Helsing, 1985, undated (Box 26)
      - Mina - Word Processor, 1985-1989, undated (Box 26)
      - July 21 1985, 1985 July 21 (Box 26)
      - September 15, 1985 (Van Helsing), 1985 September 15 (Box 26)
      - Drafts, 1985-1986, undated (Box 26)
      - The Letters of Mina Harker Original Gallies, undated; 2 (Box 26)
      - Mina Harker Royalties, 2012 (Box 26)
      - The Letters of Mina Harker Contract, undated (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian, Little Men (Hard Press, 1996), 1996, undated (Box 26)
    - Dodie Bellamy, Real: The Letters of Mina Harker and Sam D'Allesandro (Talisman House, 1994), undated (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian, Shy (Crossing Press, 1989), 1989–2005; 5 (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian and Leslie Scalapino, Stone Marmalade (Singing Horse Press, 1996), undated; 2 (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian, Tagged: Variations on a Theme (Gravity and Trajectory, 2013), 2012, undated; 5 (Box 26)
    - Kevin Killian, Tweaky Village (Wonder, 2014), undated; 2 (Box 26)
  - Unpublished works
    - 1965-A Novel, undated; 4 (Box 27)
    - Able Builing Maintenance Company, 1982-1986, undated (Box 27)
    - At the Sizzler, undated (Box 27)
    - Baby Auden, A Sex Memoir, 1984, undated (Box 27)
    - Benefit, undated (Box 27)
    - Biography, undated (Box 27)
    - Blackmail, undated; 26 (Box 27)
      Chapter titles, as recorded on folders by KK and DB: "Suffragette", "Midnight", "Carey", "Icicle on the Beach", "The Yellow Supper", "A Little Classical Music for your Kids", "Lovelita Mann", "Moth to a Flame", "Calling Sister Midnight", "The White God", "Wild Chocolate", "It's the Volcanoe", "Negroes in the Snow", "Androgynes", "The New Rythum", "Time to Unfreeze", "In Graham Greene", "Breakfast...With and Iron", "Sister Midnight", "Anticipation", "I'll Put on Some Silver", "Ishtar", "Another Time", "Rendezvouse with a Swede".
    - Jimmy, undated (Box 27)
    - Celia, undated (Box 27)
    - Gunther, undated (Box 27)
    - Julie, undated (Box 27)
    - Paula, undated (Box 27)
    - Boogie the Wonderland, undated (Box 27)
    - Hanna, undated (Box 27)
    - Joe, undated (Box 27)
    - Harry, undated (Box 27)
    - Karen, undated (Box 27)
    - Charlie, undated (Box 27)
    - Phillip, undated (Box 27)
    - "I Love New York", undated (Box 27)
    - "Especially in the Evening…", undated (Box 27)
    - Chili, undated (Box 27)
    - Jacob, undated (Box 27)
    - Slam Book 1979, undated (Box 27)
    - Germaine, undated (Box 27)
    - Nick and Cherie, undated (Box 27)
    - Shakespeare Mansions, undated (Box 27)
    - Michelle, undated (Box 27)
    - Mrs. Frazier, undated (Box 27)
    - Louise, undated (Box 27)
    - Keith Jr, undated (Box 27)
    - Bruno, undated (Box 27)
    - Wally, undated (Box 27)
    - Katherine Anne Porter, undated (Box 27)
    - Mr. Sluggo, undated (Box 27)
    - Louie, undated (Box 27)
    - Mary Lou, undated (Box 27)
    - Veronica, undated (Box 27)
    - Peter, undated (Box 27)
    - "Everybody is a Star", undated (Box 27)
    - Bernard Bacon, undated (Box 27)
    - Michael, undated (Box 27)
    - Souline, undated (Box 27)
    - Poor Professor Higgins, undated (Box 27)
    - Ruby, undated (Box 27)
    - Kiernan, undated; 2 (Box 27)
    - Blackout, undated (Box 27)
    - Jimmy and Karen, undated (Box 27)
    - Paula and Chili, undated (Box 27)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 27)
    - The Child, undated; 14 (Box 27)
      Chapter titles, as noted by KK and DB: "Variations on a Dream", "Picnic", "While you Here do Snoring Lie…", "College Girl", "Gimme Splendor", "Stray Cat Blues", "Miscarriage", "Something Natureal But Very Childish", "Hay Fever", "Cymbeline", "Marriage", "Promised Land"
    - Cigarette, undated (Box 27)
    - Bacher, Lutz, 1990-1993, undated (Box 27)
    - Cruising, undated (Box 27)
    - Dive, undated (Box 28)
    - Do the Hustle, undated (Box 28)
    - The Falcon Maltese, undated (Box 28)
    - Fascination, undated (Box 28)
    - Gunther I Need You, undated (Box 28)
    - Hotline to Heaven, undated (Box 28)
    - The Human Comedy, undated (Box 28)
    - In Every Dream Home - A Heartache, undated (Box 28)
    - Jimmy and Karen, undated (Box 28)
    - Knock on Wood, undated (Box 28)
    - Kong, undated; 2 (Box 28)
    - Little Towels, undated (Box 28)
    - The Making of, undated (Box 28)
    - Marnie and Monotheism (poem), undated (Box 28)
    - The Mayonaise Jar, undated; 2 (Box 28)
    - Milford Haven, undated (Box 28)
    - Michael Jackson, undated (Box 28)
    - Mistaken Identity (Chapter 13), undated (Box 28)
    - Narcissa, undated; 2 (Box 28)
    - Ouija Poem Wirtten by KK and 36 others, undated (Box 28)
    - The Old Wives Tale, undated (Box 28)
    - Our Mutual Friend, undated (Box 28)
    - Pickpocket/Poetryms, undated (Box 28)
    - Rebel Rebel, undated; 2 (Box 28)
    - Reptilicus, undated; 2 (Box 28)
    - The Second Chances: A Novel, undated (Box 28)
    - Secret Garden, undated (Box 28)
    - September, undated (Box 28)
    - Sleeping Head, undated (Box 28)
    - Snoring, undated (Box 28)
    - Something Good, undated (Box 28)
    - Sorrow, undated (Box 28)
    - Subterranean, undated (Box 28)
    - Tell, undated (Box 28)
    - Thank Your Lucky Stars (poem), undated (Box 28)
    - There But for the Grace of God Go I, undated (Box 28)
    - The Total Expression, undated (Box 28)
    - The Touch, undated (Box 28)
    - Universal Solider, undated (Box 28)
    - Vampire Paragraphs, undated (Box 28)
    - Vampire - Old Stuff to Collage, undated (Box 28)
    - Vampire - Extra Xeroxes, undated (Box 28)
    - White Rose, undated (Box 28)
    - Wired, undated (Box 28)
    - Wow Wow Wow Wow (original), undated (Box 28)
    - Poems 1975, undated (Box 28)
    - Kevin Killian - Unsorted Poems, undated (Box 28)
    - Writings, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Unidentified, undated; 5 (Box 28)
    - Unmailed, undated (Box 28)
    - Valentines, undated; 5 (Box 28)
    - Tweaky Village, Original, undated (Box 28)
    - Shadow Side, Original, undated (Box 28)
    - Shadow Side, Drafts, undated (Box 28)
    - My Mestiny, Original, undated (Box 28)
    - I Know the Truth, Original, undated (Box 28)
    - A Mental Melange of Melodic Memories, Original, undated (Box 28)
    - Pink Dreams, Original, undated (Box 28)
    - Gift Outright, Chapbook, undated (Box 28)
    - Bellamy-Lutz Bacher Collaboration, 1993 (Box 29)
    - Allen Dynasty, undated; 2 (Box 29)
    - Poetry Manuscripts, undated; 2 (Box 29)
- Professional papers, 1941; 1979-2015; Series III; 8.17; (8 boxes)
  - Essays, Talks, Introductions, Articles, 1979-2013, undated; 59 (Box 30)
  - Mirage / No Apologies, 1983-1985, undated; 35 (Box 30)
  - Mirage, 1989-1998, undated; 85 (Box 31)
  - Mirage, 1989-2009, undated; 88 (Box 32)
  - Work And Career, 1984-2015, undated; 60 (Box 33)
  - Blaser Moon, undated (Box 34)
  - Work And Career, 1941-2015, undated; 86 (Box 35)
  - Work And Career, 1999-2013, undated; 72 (Box 36)
  - Work And Career, 1984-2008, undated; 108 (Box 37)
- Research files, 1977-2009; Series IV; 8.88; (9 boxes)
  - Research on Sam D'Allesandro, 1977-2009, undated
    - Research files, 1977-2009, undated; 18 (Box 38)
    - Photograph of Bryan Ferry, undated (Box 39)
    - Research files, undated (Box 40)
    - Research files, undated (Box 41)
  - Research on Jack Spicer
    - Research Files
      - Abbot, Keith, 90 November 30 (Box 42)
      - Ackerman, Gerald, 1991-1998, undated; 4 (Box 42)
      - Jerry Ackerman's letters to R. Duncan, 1948, undated (Box 42)
      - Adam, Helen (Box 42)
        - Fran and George Stanley [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - George Stanley [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Jack Spicer from "The House that Jack Built" [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Lew Ellingham [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - James Alexander [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Maidens [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Ingram-Merrill Award, 1963-1964, undated (Box 42)
        - Initiation to the Magic Workshop, undated (Box 42)
      - Albon, George, 2009, undated (Box 42)
      - Alexander, Jim to Helen Adam, 1960, undated (Box 42)
      - Alexander, Paul, 1986-1997, undated; 2 (Box 42)
      - Alexander, Paul Bill Brodecky Buzz Gallery Memoir, 2002, undated (Box 42)
      - Allen, Donald, 1957-2003, undated; 17 (Box 42)
      - Donald Allen to Spicer March 23, 1952, 1952 March 23 (Box 42)
      - Don Allen to Robin Blaser, 1956-1959, undated (Box 42)
      - Alvarez, David Menendez, notes on Spicer's THE CLOCKS, 2009, undated (Box 42)
      - Ammons, A. R., 1997 January 03 (Box 42)
      - Anderson, Jack, 1991, undated (Box 42)
      - Aquatic Park [photo], undated (Box 42)
      - Aurenhahn Press, 1962-1965, undated (Box 42)
      - Austin, Edgar (Box 42)
        - Spicer exhausted negative [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Jack Spicer [photo], undated (Box 42)
      - Bancroft Library (Box 42)
        - Spicer work, Bancroft Library, 1957-2007, undated; 8 (Box 42)
        - Permissions, 2004-2008, undated; 3 (Box 42)
        - Spicer, Billy the Kid poster request to Susan Snyder, 2008 April 28 (Box 42)
      - Baraka, Amiri [Le Roi Jones], 1990–1991 (Box 42)
      - Basinski, Michael, 2007, undated (Box 42)
      - Beat Scene, Winter 2003 (Box 42)
      - Benson, Robert, 1992 August 13 (Box 42)
      - Berg, Robert (Box 42)
        - Diary, 1958, 1959· 1961, 1958–1961 (Box 42)
        - Grand Opening 6 Gallery [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Frost and Field [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Ron Primack [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Seance negatives [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Spicer at 6 Gallery opening [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Blaser on phone [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Blaser from auction [photo], undated (Box 42)
        - Field and Fagin [photo], undated (Box 42)
      - Berkeley Daily Planet (Spicer Article), 2007 September (Box 42)
      - Bertholf, Robert J., 1990-1992, undated; 5 (Box 42)
      - Bester, Alfred, 1997-1998, undated (Box 42)